>> Brian Holt: 让我向您展示有关 Redux 的部分，实际上非常，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let me show you the part
about Redux that's actually very,
在我看来很有说服力
very compelling in my opinion.
因此，我希望您安装 redux dev 工具。
So I want you to go
install redux dev tools.
>> Brian Holt: 因此我有 Firefox，所以在这里，我已经安装了它，但是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I have Firefox, so
that's here, I've already installed it but
这里也有 Chrome 的
there's also Chrome up here as well.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，我安装了那些
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
I have those installed, so
我要回到我的项目我要打开雷达克斯的设备
I'm gonna go back to my project here,
and I'm gonna open the redux dev tools.
>> Brian Holt: 你可以看到这里有一个 INIT 对象
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
you can see here there's an INIT object or
一个 INIT 的行动如果我把所有这些都删除
an INIT action that happens but
let's say if I delete all this at once,
有一个更改位置操作，您可以看到右边的位置吗 ?
there's a change location
action you can see there right?
你可以看到有一个动作改变了
And you can see that there
was an action that changes
从 CLWA 到任何内容，因此您可以看到该 dev。
from CLWA to nothing,
so you can see the dev.
你可以看到行动的样子，你可以看到国家是什么，或者
You can see what the action looks like,
you can see what the state was, or
现在的状态是这样。
the current state is like.
因此，位置为空，主题为深蓝色。
So the location is empty and
the theme is dark blue.
我可以在这里打字
And I could start typing in here, so
他们会对每个按键都采取行动吗
they'll be one action for
every keystroke right?
所以盐湖城
So Salt Lake City,
UT right?
你可以在这里看到， >> Brian Holt: 你可以
And you can see here,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You can
有点向前看但看看这个
kind of go forward, but check this out.
我可以和雷德克斯一起去旅行对吧
I can actually time travel with redux,
right?
你可以看到我的时间线如果我开始点击
So, you can see here in my timeline here,
if I started clicking back,
我从舞台上开始走回头路对吧
I start walking backwards
through my stage changes right?
然后我就能再向前走了
And then I can go forward again.
>> Brian Holt: 这就是重阳的酷，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
that's what cool about redux, right?
它允许此时间运行调试。
It allows this time traveling debugging.
所以我可以回到这里，然后我就可以点击 Play。
So I can actually just go all the way
back here, and I can just click Play.
然后就开始做我刚刚做的一切
And then it's gonna just start doing
everything that I just did back to me.
>> Brian Holt: 你知道吗，我们应该跳过那个。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And you know what,
we should probably skip that one.
所以你可以说，船长
So you can say, Skip.
>> Brian Holt: 对，所以注意到它实际上只是经过
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right, and so notice
it will actually just go through and
跳过这些然后跳到下一个
skip these and
then it'll just jump to the next one.
>> Brian Holt: 很有说服力，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Pretty compelling, right?
那么这项工作是如何进行的呢 ?
So how does this work?
这叫做事务性编程对吧
Well, this is called
transactional programming, right?
这些行动中的每一个都是技术上的交易，对吧 ?
Each one of these actions is
technically one transaction, right?
交易的关键是你能回到起点
And the thing about transactions is you
can just roll back to the beginning and
回放事务，对吗 ?
replay the transactions, right?
你不能做些交易对吧
And you can just not do some
of the transactions, right?
所以当我说要跳的时候，这其实是在做什么，对吧 ?
So what this is actually
doing when I say skip, right?
它只是经过然后说好的
It's just going through and saying okay,
就是不去申请那个，然后再申请其他的。
just don't apply that one, and
then reapply all the other ones.
同一件事如果我来改变主题我可以到这里
Same thing here, if I come and
change the theme, I can go down here and
请参阅更改主题并查看外观，这也非常酷。
see the change theme and see what that
looks like, which is pretty cool as well.
> > Brian Holt: 这里还有一个很酷的东西。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: One more
pretty cool thing here.
所以说我有这个权利我就在这里
So let's say I have this right here,
and I go here and
我可以点击上面写的测试
I can click on this thing
that says Test right here,
给我做了一个单位测试对吧
and it generated a unit test for
me, right?
我真的可以复制
I can actually literally copy and
把它贴在我的单位测试里就能为我工作了
paste this Into my unit tests and
it'll just work for me.
它正在为您生成用户测试。
It's really generating user tests for you.
用户测试?
User test?
我不知道我为什么一直说那单元是给你测试的
I don't know why I keep saying
that unit tests for you.
这是 Jest ，但也有 Mocha，磁带和 Ava 。
So this is Jest but it also does Mocha,
Tape, and Ava as well.
>> Brian Holt: 因此， dev 工具非常惊人，我看到一个公司
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So the dev tools are pretty
amazing, I saw one company what they would
如果用户发生崩溃，那么他们将转储用户的所有操作
do if a user had a crash, they would
dump all the actions that the user
已落实并将其发送至日志记录服务，因此它们实际上可以
committed and send it off to the air
logging service, so they could literally
通过所有用户正在执行的操作来导致崩溃。
step through everything that their
user was doing to cause the crash.
很酷吧
Pretty cool, right?
很有说服力
Pretty compelling.
同样地，在这种情况下，你需要对 GDPR 非常小心，
Again, with that kind of stuff you
need to be really careful with GDPR,
但还是挺酷的
but nonetheless pretty cool.